timeskuwait.com 2014-06-25

# The Times Kuwait

Privacy

In the following **Privacy Policy** , the term ‘ **TimesKuwait.com** ’ or ‘us’ or ‘we’ refers to the owner of the website whose registered office is in the State of Kuwait. The term ‘you’ refers to the user or viewer of our website.

At **TimesKuwait.com** we are committed to respecting and protecting your privacy.

When you visit **TimesKuwait.com** , you can choose to register as a member. In case you do so, we may require you to fill-in personal information during the registration process.

This privacy policy sets out the type of information we collect and how we use and protect the information that you provide.

The information we collect may include your name, age, gender, job title, company, contact details, including email, and other information relevant to customer surveys and promotional offers that run on **TimesKuwait.com**.

We use the information we collect in order to personalize our service, customize product offerings, optimize your experience, enhance security and ensure efficient administration of **TimesKuwait.com**.

In order to prevent unauthorized access or wrongful disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and administrative procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

However, **TimesKuwait.com** has no liability and is not responsible for the privacy policies, practices or content of sites that you may access from, or that may be linked to, our site. We encourage you to be aware and exert all due diligence when you visit websites that link to and from our site.

**Usage tracking**

**TimesKuwait.com** tracks users' usage in order to constantly tune the presentation and the content of its web site and offer you an optimized and customized experience when visiting our site.

**TimesKuwait.com** does not in any way correlates this statistic information with the personal information you recorded during registration. **TimesKuwait.com** uses your IP address to help diagnose any problem that you may encounter by using our server and to administrate our web site.

**TimesKuwait.com** may use cookies in order to track your usage pattern of the site. A cookie is a piece of information that is stored in your hardware drive in order to ease and customize your navigation in our web site. Cookies are in no way used to spy the content of your drives and to access personal information. Cookies are not execution programs, but only simple text files recording data that you provided while navigating in the site, such as user ID or pages you visited.

**Advertising**

**TimesKuwait.com** reserves the right to collect aggregated statistic data in order to provide advertising tools to suppliers and allow our marketing team to reach the most accurate audience. However, we guarantee you that advertisers will never have access to your personal information.

**TimesKuwait.com** reserves the right to use your e-mail address to send you information about services or products that we may consider to be of benefit to you. Should you want your e-mail address to be excluded from such mailing lists, you can choose to unsubscribe from the list or contact our marketing team through: [marketing@ **timeskuwait.com**](mailto:marketing@timeskuwait.com)

**Third party**

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our site. These online companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to our website in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit networkadvertising.org.

**TimesKuwait.com** guarantees that your personal information will NOT be disclosed, sold, rented or licensed to any external organization or third party, unless we have informed you AND fully been authorized by you.

However, should this information be required by laws and in order to respect our integrity rules, **TimesKuwait.com** reserves the right to co-operate with the Police or any other Regulatory authorities and therefore to disclose part or whole of your data to these institutions.

**Feedback and questions**

Should you have any additional questions or comments on this Privacy Policy, feel free to contact our marketing team on [marketing@t **imeskuwait.com**](mailto:marketing@timeskuwait.com). Please also visit our **Disclaimer** and **Terms and Conditions** **of Usage** sections that establish the use, disclaimer and limitations of liability governing further use of kuwiatindiatimes.com.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and update the Privacy Policy modification date shown below. 

By using our site, you consent to the privacy policy of t **imeskuwait.com**.

This policy was last modified on 1st October, 2011 [http://www. **timeskuwait.com**](http://www.timeskuwait.com/)

"It's by one's own actions that we clearly define our existence, our reality and ultimately the outcome. Seek truth, build character, find happiness and most of all share and be grateful to those that encouraged you to never give up!"

Take yourself seriously. You can't make any real progress, for as long as you keep belittling your own accomplishments.

Photo Gallery
